Jack, you going camping with your friends this weekend?
It depends. If it's sunny, we'll go.
The weatherman says it's going to rain.
In that case, we'll go to the cinema instead.
Excuse me, could you mind my bags for a moment?
I want to buy some food at the convenience store.
No problem, but be quick.
It was announced that my train would arrive in ten minutes.
Bob came out of last Friday.
Have you got a chance to visit him?
I plan to see him this Saturday.
Aren't you going to the conference then?
No, it has been rescheduled for next Monday.
Sorry, miss. We made a terrible mistake adding up the bill.
Here is the ten dollars we have to return to you.
Oh, I didn't notice that.
It's okay. Don't blame the waiter.
He's been really nice.
Do you think we should get Steve a book for the new year?
are good, but Steve wouldn't take just any book.
He has to have this particular one on geography.
Hello, Sarah. Hello, David.
I can't come for dinner tonight.
Sorry. Oh, what happened?
We've got a new case and things get pretty crazy here in the office.
Well, then I'll come to you.
No, no, not tonight.
Let me see if I can arrange another night.
Sarah, please. We need to talk.
It's about my job.
Then tell me on the phone.
No, it's better if we do it in person.
How about tomorrow night?
I'm not sure.
You can give me a tomorrow afternoon.
Okay. Hello, Sarah.
Hello, David. I can't come for dinner tonight.
Sorry. Oh, what happened?
We've got a new case and things get pretty crazy here in the office.
Well, then I'll come to you.
No, no, not tonight.
Let me see if I can arrange another night.
Sarah, please. We need to talk.
It's about my job.
Then tell me on the phone.
No, it's better if we do it in person.
How about tomorrow night?
I'm not sure.
You can give me a call tomorrow afternoon.
Okay. Jim will call on us this afternoon.
Do you know where he is now?
Er, wait. Let me see.
He has sent two messages saying that he's done with his work at the office and got a
and he'll arrive in 20 minutes.
We can't keep him waiting outside our home.
We have to hurry.
But it takes at least half an hour to get out of the city centre by bus.
Look at the traffic.
Let's get off.
We can save at least 20 minutes by walking through the park.
Are you sure?
Yes, a hundred percent.
Jim will call on us this afternoon.
Do you know where he is now?
Er, wait. Let me see.
He has sent two messages saying that he's done with his work at the office and got a
taxi and he'll arrive in 20 minutes.
We can't keep him waiting outside our home.
We have to hurry.
But it takes at least half an hour to get out of the city centre by bus.
Look at the traffic.
Let's get off.
We can save at least 20 minutes by walking through the park.
Are you sure?
Yes, a hundred percent.
Morning, Mark. Morning, Clara.
How was your weekend?
Great. I went to my grandpa's.
He invited us to pick vegetables on his farm.
My daughter had a great time there.
What about you?
Oh, I had a truly incredible experience.
I dropped by a yard sale on Saturday and got several books.
Novels? A novel and two poetry collections.
I leafed through the novel, a piece of paper fell out.
It was an air ticket from 2012.
The flight was from Los Angeles to Chicago and the name on the ticket was Ashley
Lewis. Was it?
Yes. Ashley, my sister.
In 2012 she lived in Los Angeles and her husband worked in Chicago.
Both of them often flew between the two cities.
I asked the seller where he got the book.
He said it was bought at a secondhand bookstore in Los Angeles three years ago.
Last year he and his family moved from Los Angeles to Philadelphia.
all the way across the country your sister's old book landed in your hands.
That's really crazy.
Morning, Mark. Morning, Clara.
How was your weekend?
Great. I went to my grandpa's.
He invited us to pick vegetables on his farm.
My daughter had a great time there.
What about you?
Oh, I had a truly incredible experience.
I dropped by a yard sale on Saturday and got several books.
Novels? A novel and two poetry collections.
I leafed through the novel a piece of paper fell out.
It was an air ticket from 2012.
The flight was from Los Angeles to Chicago and the name on the ticket was Ashley
Lewis. Was it?
Yes. Ashley, my sister.
In 2012 she lived in Los Angeles and her husband worked in Chicago.
Both of them often flew between the two cities.
I asked the seller where he got the book.
He said it was bought at a secondhand bookstore in Los Angeles three years ago.
Last year he and his family moved from Los Angeles to Philadelphia.
all the way across the country your sister's old book landed in your hands.
That's really crazy.
Victor, you've been here in Indiana for six weeks now.
How are you feeling?
I think I've got used to college life.
Going to classes, working out and hanging out with my friends.
Though there's pressure to meet deadlines, life here is never boring.
What's been hard about being an Indiana basketball player?
Well, the training is very competitive.
Weightlifting and running every day.
It's not like high school.
In high school I really didn't have to do that.
I'm just trying to get used to it and I think I am.
At this point how do you see yourself fitting into this group?
I think we are all different.
George is from Britain, Chris and Leo are from Australia, I'm from France and the
rest are Americans.
But I get along with everybody.
You know, we are really starting to bond.
It's great to see how we grow each day as a team.
Thanks, Victor. I wish you a very happy and fruitful stay in Indiana.
Victor, you've been here in Indiana for six weeks now.
How are you feeling?
I think I've got used to college life.
Going to classes, working out and hanging out with my friends.
Though there's pressure to meet deadlines, life here is never boring.
What's been hard about being an Indiana basketball player?
Well, the training is very competitive.
Weightlifting and running every day.
It's not like high school.
In high school I really didn't have to do that.
I'm just trying to get used to it and I think I am.
At this point how do you see yourself fitting into this group?
I think we are all different.
George is from Britain, Chris and Leo are from Australia, I'm from France and the
rest are Americans.
But I get along with everybody.
You know, we are really starting to bond.
It's great to see how we grow each day as a team.
Thanks, Victor. I wish you a very happy and fruitful stay in Indiana.
Good evening, dear listeners.
When was the last time you enjoyed leisure activities?
Do you want to a full and happy life?
Today I am going to introduce to you a magazine that features the art of living.
The Idler was launched by Tom Hockenson back in 1993 with the intention of providing
a bit of fun, freedom and achievement in a busy world.
It is now published bi -monthly.
In every issue you'll find an interesting mix of interviews and essays on the good
life, history, philosophy, arts and fashion photography.
You'll find much to laugh at and much useful stuff as well, from recipes for making
bacon to guides to housekeeping.
If you've ever felt that there's more to life than boring jobs, then why not
subscribe to it?
The Idler is a cheering read that makes you feel better about life.
You can download the application and subscribe today to get your first issue free.
Good evening, dear listeners.
When was the last time you enjoyed leisure activities?
Do you want to a full and happy life?
Today I am going to introduce to you a magazine that features the art of living.
The Idler was launched by Tom Hockenson back in 1993 with the intention of providing
a bit of fun, freedom and achievement in a busy world.
It is now published bi -monthly.
In every issue you'll find an interesting mix of interviews and essays on the good
life, history, philosophy, arts and fashion photography.
You'll find much to laugh at and much useful stuff as well, from recipes for making
bacon to guides to housekeeping.
If you've ever felt that there's more to life than boring jobs, then why not
subscribe to it?
The Idler is a cheering read that makes you feel better about life.
You can download the application and subscribe today to get your first issue free.